<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Maigo's Release Feed</title>
		<description>Written manually. Because I'm a dumbass.</description>
		<link>http://maigo.us</link>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 10</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/s1l3gxm2t7fhqct/Gonensei_v02_c10_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
       <item>
			<title>Taiyou no Ie Chapter 45</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/zc9kem8ki4yenny/Taiyou_no_Ie_c45_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>O/A Chapter 31</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/ch9jxfjumufvcyx/OA_v07_c31_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
       
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 9</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>https://mega.co.nz/#!oBJAzRzR!gDD8Yknj4hSPVHwa1fJDiSToUd4q02h6a5EvIV6VExE</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Hakoiri Drops Chapter 1</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/82jyyty7twyn4cw/Hakoiri_Drops_v01_c01_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
         <item>
			<title>Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Chapter 44.5</title>
			<description>The other day, I went to Red Lobster for the first time. If you mention Red Lobster on, say, Twitter, do you know what's the first thing everybody mentions? That's right: the cheese biscuits. It's quite the dangerous trap. I ended up eating so many biscuits that I had to take half my entree home. Just what is the allure of those biscuits? It's very mysterious, but I digress. Haganai 44.5 is a special short chapter starring Sena.</description>
            <link>http://www.batoto.net/read/_/264216/boku-wa-tomodachi-ga-sukunai_ch44.5_by_maigo</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 8</title>
			<description>There's not much use in worrying about problems you can't solve, but knowing that doesn't make it any easier to deal with them. Sometimes you try to move forward as hard as you can, but it's all you can do to keep your head above the surface. Akio treads water and watches the world pass him by.</description> 
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/lhfpl4dmlyn4c7d/Gonensei_v02_c08_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
    
        <item>
			<title>Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Chapter 44</title>
			<description>Lately, I've been trying to get back into 立直 mahjong. One habit I can't really break, though, is that I always tend to go for a 平和 hand without really thinking. They may be a bit easy to read, but there's nothing like the sense of peace when you make a 平和 hand, especially if you manage to get to 一向聴 with two 両面 shapes just waiting to be filled. It's really the best. Anyway, Haganai. This chapter marks the start of the school festival arc.</description>
            <link>http://www.batoto.net/read/_/263717/boku-wa-tomodachi-ga-sukunai_ch44_by_maigo</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Natsu no Zenjitsu Volume 4 Omake</title>
			<description>The fifth (<em>and possibly final</em>) volume will be here soon&#8482;.</description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/efb3ilooxzm61h2/Natsu_no_Zenjitsu_v04_Omake_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 7</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/7qiex0oj3674bwn/Gonensei_v02_c07_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 6</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/diw9d94zd6p7spi/Gonensei_v01_c06_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 5</title>
			<description></description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/847hr474d63y8rd/Gonensei_v01_c05_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 4</title>
			<description>
@AnonSpore: Some people do insert the mental comma with word bubble split, but there's nothing to be lost from inserting it manually; it's not like those people suddenly have double commas in their mental landscapes.
!Kiiragi: i think everyone inserts it
@AnonSpore: I don't. So what do you think? Not that it really matters since Spore gets to do what Spore wants because he's unicellular.</description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/ka96kfl7br94j5k/Gonensei_v01_c04_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
                
        <item>
			<title>Kekkon Yubiwa Monogatari Chapter 4</title>
			<description>Maybe maybe should put some more thought into that fantasy world of his instead of ripping off the medieval lore we've seen done a googolplex times already. Still, his romance antics are top-notch, and this chapter cements his reigning status as the one true vanilla king. Sigh. All hail maybe.</description>
            <link>http://www.mediafire.com/download/swtm42w5w3x847f/Kekkon_Yubiwa_Monogatari_c4_[Maigo].zip</link>
		</item>
                
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 3</title>
			<description>But really, think for yourself. Don't live life by quotes. They're just another perspective.</description>
            <link>https://mega.co.nz/#!oVhSWIqa!rau-TwqcVMIonYSyr6axLGNNIbRjnuSbmzlkFgwjkew</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 2</title>
			<description>"Life is too short to wake up in the morning with regrets. So, love the people who treat you right and forget about the ones who don't. And believe that everything happens for a reason... if you get a chance - take it; if it changes your life - let it. Nobody said that it would be easy... They just promised it would be worth it."</description>
            <link>https://mega.co.nz/#!MRJjySyJ!auIIGhJ3a-azSuKe89qI2EGapobhqHsRshjXA44IAb0</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tetsugaku Letra Chapter 13</title>
            <description>Flamenco is a form of Spanish folk music and dance from the region of Andalusia in southern Spain. In recent years, flamenco has become popular all over the world and is taught in many countries: in Japan there are more academies than there are in Spain.</description>	
            <link>https://mega.co.nz/#!JVBn0aSL!e4MUmfpiQh8_vM8L2iSlcigWShMaTI48pPI0_Lhjn7I</link>
        </item>
        
		<item>
			<title>Gonensei Chapter 1</title>
			<description>The sequel to Yonensei. Akio and Yoshino believed all there was left for them was to graduate. But life had different plans for them. Yoshino moves on while Akio stays behind, and something between them begins to change. The story of their youth continues.</description>	   
            <link>https://mega.co.nz/#!gJIEGTSD!NiWrEXD1ZCAzPR7evZfhC7vxWUjhQe32iAFyk7HW2s0</link>
		</item>
            
        <item>
			<title>Boku wa Tomodachi ga Sukunai Chapter 43</title>
			<description>Kobato's birthday party is in full swing.
And uh, we need more redrawers. And letterers. 
Just experienced people in general.</description>
			<link>http://www.batoto.net/read/_/261216/boku-wa-tomodachi-ga-sukunai_ch43_by_maigo</link>
		</item>
        
        <item>
			<title>Taiyou no Ie Volume 10 Bangai-hen</title>
			<description>Being Radical is suffering. The main story will return in a few weeks.</description>
			<link>https://mega.co.nz/#!QYxkFLLT!DwIFQftnfFzOiqm7-BJ-_AdUDfVnDoL_TF3QD2Qz9ys</link>
		</item>
        
	</channel>
</rss>